Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records, 1916-1949 and undated RL.11720
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Signed Estimates, 1938-1949; 7
  - Selecciones del Reader's Digest, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Sharp & Dohme, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Shell Chemical, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Shell Oil, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Shell Oil, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Shell Oil, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Shell Oil, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Shell Oil, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Shell Oil, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Skol, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Skol, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Skol, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Squibb, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Squibb, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Squibb, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Standard Brands, 1938-1940 (Reel 881)
  - Standard Brands, 1940-1946 (Reel 882)
    See duplicate reel 895
  - Standard Brands, 1946-1947 (Reel 883)
  - Standard Brands, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Standard Brands--Chase & Sanborn, Tender Leaf, 1949 (Reel 872)
  - Standard Brands--Fleischmann's Yeast, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Surplus Property Office, U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1947 (Reel 764)
  - Swift, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Swift, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Swift, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Tap Icer, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Textron, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Textron, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Textron, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Textron, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Textron, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Textron, 1949 (Reel 872)
  - Thompson Products, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Trust Company of Old Greenwich, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - U.S. Brewers Foundation, 1949 (Reel 872)
  - U.S. Lines, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - U.S. Lines, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - U.S. Lines, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - U.S. Lines, 1947 (Reel 764)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - U.S. Playing Card, 1949 (Reel 872)
  - United Artists, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - United Artists, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - United Cut Flower, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - United Cut Flower, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - United Medical Service, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Universal Pictures, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Universal Pictures, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Universal Pictures, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - Vimms, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Vimms, 1944 (Reel 756)
  - Vimms, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - W.F. Young, 1944 (Reel 756)
  - W.F. Young, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - W.F. Young, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - W.F. Young, 1948 (Reel 768)
  - Ward Baking, 1944 (Reel 756)
  - Ward Baking, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Ward Baking, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - Ward Baking, 1947 (Reel 764)
  - Ward Baking, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - Washington Consultant Services, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Webb Young Trader, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Webb Young Trader, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - Webb Young Trader, 1947 (Reel 764)
  - Webb Young Trader, 1948 (Reel 768)
  - Weco Products (Dr. West toothbrush), 1947 (Reel 764)
  - Western Union, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - Western Union, 1948 (Reel 768)
  - Women's National Republican Club, 1948 (Reel 768)
- Talent Payment Department, 1937-1949; 8
  - "Rights" cards, 1948 (Reel 420)
  - "Rights" cards, 1949 (Reel 421)
  - Client cards, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Employee cards, 1941 (Reel 226)
  - Model and musician expense cards, 1939-1940 (Reel 227)
  - Model cards, 1938 (Reel 229)
  - Model cards, 1941 (Reel 226)
  - Musician cards, 1938 (Reel 228)
  - Musician cards, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Musician cards, 1937-1938 (Reel 229)
  - Radio talent expense cards (not in alphabetical order), 1941 (Reel 219)
  - Radio talent expense cards (not in alphabetical order), 1944 (Reel 216)
  - Radio talent expense cards (not in alphabetical order), 1942-1943 (Reel 218)
  - State tax and control charts, 1948 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards, 1945 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards, 1946 (Reel 335)
  - Wage cards, 1948 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards (A-C), 1949 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards (A-Fite), 1947 (Reel 335)
  - Wage Cards (beginning with Fitzmaurice), 1947 (Reel 336)
  - Wage cards (D-L), 1949 (Reel 421)
  - Wage cards (M-Z), 1949 (Reel 421)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1937 (Reel 229)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1938 (Reel 228)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1941 (Reel 226)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1944 (Reel 216)
    See also reel 219 for more; reel 217 (betwween letters C and D) for: William Adams, Ralph Colicchio, Toshe Samaroff
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1939-1940 (Reel 227)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1941 (Reel 375)
    A's; see reel 219 for rest
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1941-1944 (Reel 219)
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1942-1943 (Reel 217)
    Through Roland MacLane; continued on reel 218; Radcliffe Hall on reel 218 between Q and R
  - Wage cards (roughly alphabetical)--Radio talent, investigators, models, 1942-1943 (Reel 218)
    Begins with MacMillan; continued on reel 219
  - Wage cards--Aileen Pringle, 1937 (Reel 271)
    Retakes from reel 229 (originals blurry)
  - Wage cards--Bing Crosby, 1938-1940 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Frank Sinatra, 1944 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards--Helen Crocker, 1948 (Reel 421)
  - Wage cards--Irene Purchell, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Louis Sarin, 1945 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards--Margaret Seddon, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Mildred Horn, 1948 (Reel 421)
  - Wage cards--Models, 1948 (Reel 420)
  - Wage cards--Rolf Sedan, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Rosa Tentoni, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Rose Schneiderman, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Shelton Howard (Sealtest), 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--Verna Powell, 1937 (Reel 271)
  - Wage cards--William Quinn, 1937 (Reel 271)